winithemes.com 2013-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Winithemes

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is our top concern, thus we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

  1. We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.
  2. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology.

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal data and other information we receive from Users of the Site.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and after that we will handle your personal data in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy that was in force when you submitted them. We will notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy by posting the new version of the Privacy Policy on the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on the home page of the Site.

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use. By continuing to use the Site after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the Site in the manner described above, you are consenting to these changes. You willingly provide us certain personal data, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the Site functionalities. If you have any hesitation about providing such personal data to us or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms of Use, you should not become a User of the Site.

## The Site and Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Site. The Site may contain links to third parties' sites which are not owned or controlled by the Owner. The Owner has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies (if any), or practices of any third parties' sites. You acknowledge that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third parties' sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release the Owner from any and all liability arising from your use of any third parties' sites to which this Site may link.

Our primary goals in collecting your personal data are to provide and improve the Site and the related features, to administer your subscription and to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. Below are the types and categories of information we collect.

## Personal Data Collected

We collect your personal data in the following ways:

## Registration

In order to become a User, you do not need to create an account on the Site. However, in order to access some features of the Site you will have to create an account. When creating your account you benefit from additional services we provide through the Site. To create an account you are required to provide the following information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge are personal data allowing others, including the Owner, to identify you: login, e-mail address, and a password chosen by you.

We may also ask you to provide additional information after you register if you want to obtain additional services or information or to resolve complaints or concerns. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of any personal information you submit. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using the Site and tools and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to associate an account managed by a third party with your account on the Site you hereby authorizes us to have access to personal data stored by third parties such as Facebook, Google+ or Twitter and you agree that we may collect, store and use these personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Scope and categories of personal data we may receive in this case depends on policies of third parties’ sites and is controlled by these third parties (these personal data may include, but are not limited to, your name, gender, profile photo, location/hometown, website, email address and other information you make publicly available via the social networking sites). For example, the Site allows you to create an account and login to the service using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as a user of the Site and you click on “Sign in Using Facebook,” you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join the Site.

## Forums, message boards, Q&A, groups, etc.

When you post any message to a forum, message board, Q&A, group or any other public forum within the Site where User can post his/her observations and comments on designated topics, your basic information will be available for all registered Users to see. This basic information consists of your username. You should not post any information about you or any other person to a forum, message board, Q&A, group or other public forums within the Site if you want to keep such information private or you are required by law to do so. Information you post to public forums within the Site is considered public information and may be used by us and third parties. As with any public forum on any site, this information may also appear in third party search engines like Google, Yahoo, MSN etc. We do not control the information indexed and cached by search engines.

## Surveys

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research and to improve the Site, although you do not have to respond to them.

## Log Data

When you visit the Site, whether as a registered User or a non-registered User just browsing, our servers automatically record information about your use and your visit to the Site ("Log Data"). The Log Data may include information such as your computer Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what software you were using, the web page you were visiting immediately prior to visiting the Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze the use of the Site and for the Site's technical administration, to improve the Site's functionalities and User-friendliness, and to better tailor it to the Users' needs.

## Cookies

Like most sites, we use cookies and web log files to track the use of the Site. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer and allows the Owner to recognize you as a User when you return to the Site using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you may not be able to use the Site. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data are used to customize your experience on the Site.

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your account. The next time you visit the Site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as a registered User, so you will not need to log in before using the Site.

Additionally, if you log out of your account you will need to re-enter your password the next time in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. Moreover, the Site may use local shared objects, commonly called a "flash cookies" for purposes such as storing Users’ preferences. You may manage or opt out of your flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html).

In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third parties, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the Site. The Owner does not store personal data in the cookies.

## Web Beacons

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Users through the Site. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

To deliver these ads properly, we may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by the Owner so the ad networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other sites.

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other sites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. The Owner does not provide personal data to any advertiser or any other third parties.

## Log files, IP and Information About Your Computer

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Site. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, e-mail patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Site. The linkage between your IP address and your personal data is not shared with third parties without your prior consent or except when allowed or required by law.

## Communications

The Owner will communicate with you through e-mail and notices posted on the Site or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). Please be aware that you will always receive certain e-mails from the Owner related to the proper functioning of your account. You can change your e-mail at any time by logging into your "Account".

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

The Owner takes the privacy of Users very seriously. Thus, we do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personal data with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. For example, we may hire other companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in marketing, to conduct audits, etc. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personal data except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the use of the Site to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on the Site.

We may share the information in your account on the Site (including your personal data) with the third parties’ site that you have linked to your account on the Site. These third parties have access to your personal data only for this purpose (unless third parties have received your personal data independently of the Site) and not for other purposes.

## Teaming with Third Parties

The Owner allows other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your use of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect the information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone are not considered as personal data and generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are, unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

## Legal Disclaimer

The Owner cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation a court action), to protect the property and rights of the Owner or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

## Disclosures to Others

The Owner may also disclose your personal data and other information you provide, to another third party as part of reorganization or a sale of the assets of the Owner's division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell our assets will have the right to continue to use the personal data and other information that you provide to us.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the Owner. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, or login password in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or mobile devices communication.

## Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include personal data and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal data.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers and servers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your consent to such transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to those third parties' web sites. The fact that we link to a web site or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third parties' web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect personal data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal data you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies (if any) or statements of the other web sites you visit.

## Accessing and Changing your Account Information

You can review the information you provided us and make any desired changes to them at any time by logging in to your account on the Site. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, the Owner may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by emailing us using the following Contact Form.

## Deleting your Account

You can also delete your account. If you delete your account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law.In order to delete your account please submit a relevant declaration of intent through the following [Contact Form](http://winithemes.com/contact).

## Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations:

  1. You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.
  2. You must not download, upload or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic.

Any violation of these obligations may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your use of the Site and/or your account by the Owner, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which the Users adhere to the Site and the services which it offers.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Owner may update this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice.

If you use the Site after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the Site, you hereby provide your consent to these changes.

## Security

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable laws related to security breach notification) to you via e-mail or conspicuous posting on the Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with: (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement; or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## Data Retention Policy

The Owner may retain your personal data and account information indefinitely, regardless of whether you have disabled your account on the Site. The Owner will retain Log Data consistent with applicable legal requirements. Generally, at a minimum, the Owner will retain the Log Data collected from you in its active, internal company databases for six months, at which point it will migrate such Log Data to its offline archival systems, where The Owner will retain the Log Data for a period of three years (together, the "Retention Period"). After the Retention Period, the Owner will purge the Log Data from its systems. In the event of an investigation by law enforcement or a response to claims or legal process, the Owner may retain the Log Data until such investigation or process is completed, which may be longer than the Retention Period.

## Statement

In accordance with the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data (consolidated text: Journal of Laws of 2002 No 101, item 926 as amended), the data controller of your personal data is the Owner, that is Red Sky Sp. z o.o., a company duly incorporated under the laws of Poland, with its registered office in Szczecin, at Aleja Piastów 22, Szczecin, 71-064, Poland, entered into the register of entrepreneurs of the National Court Register maintained by the District Court Szczecin-Centrum in Szczecin – the Commercial Court, XIII Commercial Department of the National Court Register, with KRS number 0000209107, NIP (tax identification number): 6422683651, and REGON number 276822679.

The Owner hereby declares as follows:

  1. All data provided in a Contact Form and/or a Register Form will be processed in order to allow the use of the Site. All data provided to the Owner will be stored and processed by the Owner in accordance with the provisions of the Polish Act of 18 July 2002 on providing services by electronic means (Journal of Laws of 2002 No 144, item 1204 as amended), as well as in accordance with the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data.
  2. All personal data provided to the Owner will be stored in the Owner's database.
  3. The Owner shall ensure the safety of Users’ personal data and the Owner has implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures as set forth in the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data and has met the requirements specified in the provisions referred to thereof, in particular to protect the personal data to be processed against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network, and against all other unlawful forms of processing. These measures ensure a level of security appropriate to the risks presented by the processing and the nature of the data to be protected having regard to the state of the art.
  4. Users have the right to verify, review and correct their personal data processed by the Owner. The right can be exercised by a User by sending a relevant request using the following Contact Form.
  5. Users have the right to withdraw their consent to the processing of their personal data, giving the Owner a notice to that effect. Though Users provide their personal data to the Owner voluntarily, refusal to provide them renders entry into the agreement with the Owner and access to the Site impossible.
  6. The Owner fulfils all the requirements of the Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data.
  7. The Owner shall have the right to disclose the personal data only to the authorities entitled under the provisions of the law in force (e.g. a court, the police).
  8. Personal data provided to the Owner in a Contact Form and/or a Register Form or in any other way will be used by the Owner and its affiliates exclusively for the following purposes: (i) User's use of and registration on the Site (a possibility of using the functionalities offered by the Site which includes resolving disputes, preventing prohibited or illegal activities; a User is a party to the agreement on services provided by electronic means); (ii) processing complaints and providing customer support; (iii) contacting Users and replying to correspondence sent through the Contact Form; (iv) technical operation of the Site; (v) direct marketing (based on User’s preferences); (vi) maintaining the Site’s statistics; (vii) displaying the content that is customized to User’s interests and preferences; (viii) performing research and analysis aimed at improving the Site; (ix) running contests, selecting entrants, and choosing prize winners.

After reviewing the above Privacy Policy, by using or accessing the Site, and especially by clicking the "REGISTER" button during the registration process, you hereby:

  1. Consent to the processing and use by the Owner all the personal data provided to the Owner, including data obtained as a result of your use of the Site, for the above mentioned purposes.
  2. Consent to transfer of your personal data abroad, and in particular to the Owner affiliated companies or associated entities, or to the Owner’s parent company, with their registered office outside the Poland, for the purposes of processing in computer systems belonging to the Owner and its business partners. You understand that the above entities may be located in countries that do not guarantee the same level of personal data protection as the level guaranteed in Poland.
  3. Agree that your consent remains valid for the entire period of your use of the Site.
  4. Declare and confirm that you have read the Terms of Use, you understand them and you will comply with them, both in its current wording and with any later amendments.

## How to contact us

If you have any queries regarding your personal data or comments on this Privacy Policy, please email us using the following [Contact Form](http://winithemes.com/contact).
